An Idea.
A Concept.
A Plan.
A Dream.
That's how businesses start.
With the help of the U.S.
Small Business Administration
businesses transform.
From a home office,
to a global operation.
A double-oven setup,
to a six person bakery.
Concept to manufacturing.
And from contemplating
closure, to not just surviving,
but thriving. That's the power
of the SBA.
We make small business
our business
By being an ally, an advocate
a mentor a coach, an educator,
a friend.
To ambitious and passionate
entrepreneurs
and we're igniting change,
sparking action,
so businesses across the nation
can confidently
start, grow, expand,
and recover.
SBA, empowering small
businesses and
powering the American Dream.
[Music]